You're a Poisoner, Dio Brando.
I have all the proof I
require, and then some!
He's found his proof, so be it.
This moment's been a
long time coming, JoJo.
Now, I finish what I started!
Let's go.
I'm the star-sponsor of the world?.
and I'll keep you together!.
I'm the star-sponsor of the world!.
The star-sponsor of the world!.
The star-sponsor
of
the
world?.
I tracked down the antidote.
Father took it moments ago.
Dio, this pains me greatly.
For years, you were my brother, and now
I have no recourse but to turn you in.
I'm sorry.
Really, I'm sure you don't believe a word
of it, but I'm telling you the truth.
Even now you show compassion
Jojo I've been a devil
but grant me this one wish
allow me to do the right
thing for once in my life And
turn myself in what's this
I thought once I confronted
him he'd fight me tooth and
nail like a cornered beast.
Jojo,
you should be dead in a gutter right? now.
I must distract him long enough
with a knife and mask to find
their mark.
My wicked deeds gnaw at me.
The poverty I Knew as a child ate away at
my moral compass until greed was all that
remained.
I'm the lowest of the low.
Your father took me in off the street
and I repaid his kindness with poison.
The only reason I came back
was to surrender myself.
If I'd wanted to flee, You never
would have laid eyes on me again.
I see your point.
Please allow me to make amends.
Deal.
Look alive, Master Joestar.
He's trying to lure you in like he's not.
Right about now, you're
probably wondering who I am.
Allow me to elucidate you.
The name is Robert E .O. Speedwagon.
I had a hunch Jonathan's run
of trouble might not be done,
so I followed him back home.
I like you, Jonathan, so I'm going to
offer up this little tidbit pro bono.
Living in the gutter,
you learn to spot lowlights pretty
quick if you want to see tomorrow.
I've trained my nose to sort out the bad
ones from the good just from a sniff.
This Fool reeks of brimstone and blood
worse than anyone I've ever laid eyes on.
He is pure evil, right
down to his very bones.
Is he a victim of
circumstance, you're wondering?
Not on your life!
He's been evil since he
drew his first breath.
But don't you fret, because I
brought you a friend. Remember him?
This man confessed to selling you
the poison you used on Father.
I've heard enough.
You break my heart.
Why, dear, from the day you arrived, I have
loved you as though you were my own son.
Father you're too weak to be down here
you're right i'll return to my chamber.
I don't want to see my
boy in chains do what
you must Jojo i will is
this how it all ends?
He won't see the inside
of a cell this night i
read his face and the
trio of moors on his ear.
The devil smiles on him
and grants him luck.
Jojo, I want you to be the
one to put the cuffs on me.
Please, brother.
All right.
Be careful, he's a crafty one.
Jojo, it was hubris that led
me to this ignominious end.
This fall from grace has taught me well.
However one may scheme and dissemble,
my downfall this night is
part of the human condition.
A condition I now forsake.
Wait, forsake? What do you mean?
You see, I am about to
become so much more!
Help me shed this mortal skin!
Mother's mask? But how?
Watch out!
Fire at will, man!
Jojo, your blood is the key!
Oh, my God!
Fulver!
Shoot that maniac!
Jojo.
Father.
This is all my fault.
I should have blocked his knife.
The mask.
When I saw it, I froze up.
And you paid the price.
Take this ring.
It was your mother's, Jojo.
Father.
Damn it!
Ain't a doctor on Earth who can fix that.
How'd that devil get the drop on us?
It's all my fault!
If only I hadn't listened
to you, Sir Joestar!
If I had run his father out of town
years ago like I'd have mind to,
none of this would have taken
place! Hold on. Whose father?
Back when I first joined the Force,
there was a ne 'er-do-well
who tried to pawn
that very ring you now
see on Joestar's finger.
The suspect was Dio's
birth father, Dario Brando.
It's mine, of that there's no doubt.
My late wife and I had them
made to celebrate our betrothal.
A local cut purse by the name of
Dario Brando was trying to sell it.
Can it be?
Sir Joestar thought he owed his life
to Dario, but he was sadly mistaken.
Dario hadn't scrambled down to the mangled
carriage that fateful night
to look for survivors,
but to root for ill-gotten riches.
You stay back!
This man, what has he said, Inspector?
Did he ever tell you
that I gave him the ring?
Aye, he swore up and down.
You filthy liar!
He swore with good reason.
I gave him the ring, just as he told you.
You have got to be kidding!
He is innocent.
Let him go at once, Inspector.
But, sir, this man stole from you.
But for Providence's hand in my life,
I might as well have done the same.
Sell this ring, if you may ease
your family's burden by it.
Walk an honest path henceforth,
and I give it gladly.
He knew he didn't owe Dario a damn thing.
And he took Dio in all the same.
Father, hang on.
The doctor's on his way now.
Jojo, don't hate Dio for what he's done.
I am to blame for this.
I was hard on you.
Because you were a Joestar.
I went too easy on Dio.
And he might have felt I didn't care.
Perhaps he did this for
want of a father's love.
Please.
See that he's buried.
Next to Dario.
Father.
Don't look so sad, Jojo.
We're better to die Than
in the arms Of my son.
The Joestar!
We have lost much this night.
A noble man's soul has
been taken from the world.
You're wrong!
All that was good in that man,
he passed it along to Jonathan?
every bit of it!
You can be sure, Jojo's
gonna live an upright life?
using what his father gave him.
Rich folks are rubbish.
Watching them flounce around, I wanna throw
the whole lot of them into the Thames.
But not the Joestars.
The heroic and merciful and just the
whole damn lot are giants among men.
What the hell?
The body!
Dio's corpse, it...
It vanished!
Oi, Grip!
Away from the window!
The inspector!
No, that's impossible.
How is he alive?
It can't be.
We all filled him full of bullets.
Keep your distance, lads.
He's armed with something.
Was it the mosque?
He's coming right at us!
What are you waiting for?
Hit him with everything you've got left!
Come no closer!
Not another step!
I mean it!
Blow his brains out now!
Do it before he kills us all!
Shot him in the head and it
didn't even slow him down.
It doesn't make any sense!
With all the lead we put in him
he should be worm food by now.
How can this be?
Jojo, I should thank you for
the source of my newfound power,
your father's blood, and the ancient mask.
He takes his very life,
but how is that possible?
Dio, you villain.
What sort of monster have you become?
How did this happen?
Think, Jojo, think!
The knife, father, blood,
Dio, the mask, my notes, the brain,
unknown abilities, unknown strength!
There is nothing human left of you, Dio!
Don't do it, Jojo!
You haven't got a chance in hell!
I've never seen anything like this lad.
He broke those coppers to pieces
like they were fleeting twigs!
I know.
Honestly, I'm terrified.
All the same, I can't
let Dio kill anyone else!
This demon must be annihilated!
Please, Jojo, I beg of you!
He'll tear you apart!
That's it.
According to my research on the mask,
it was fabled to unlock the
brain's hidden potential.
To vanquish Dio, all I have to do is...
This one's alive.
Your blood.
It smells so delicious.
Now, I'm going to turn you inside out.
He was my brother.
Look at him now, father.
Please lend me the
strength to do what I must.
Courage, Jojo.
Dio is powerful, but
you know how to end him.
And end him you must!
Watch out!
It's over!
I'm not going to let you
kill anyone else! Dio!
He caught the sword and spear.
Right through the hand
and he don't even flinch.
No way, the hole from where
I shot him in the head?
It's healed up.
That spear ain't gonna hurt him.
He's immortal.
You're such a weakling, Jojo?
On your feet, insect.
I've yet to gauge the full
extent of my new powers.
So let's play a little longer, shall we?
I trust you'll be long since dead
by the time I figure them out.
Hiding, are we?
You were a fool to attack me.
I have disowned my weakness
in favor of life everlasting.
You're behind the curtain
like Polonius and like
Polonius it is there that
you shall meet your end!
No one's immortal not even you.
He's able to heal faster
than the flames can hurt him.
If that ain't immortality,
then I'm the queen.
Fire hurts him, but not enough.
Jojo, what are you doing?
Just get to safety, Speedwagon.
If Dio wants a fight,
I mean to give him one.
What are you doing?
Are you mad?
The flames are gonna box you in up there!
Jojo, you brave fool!
I hope to hell you've got a plan?
I'm waiting for you, Dio.
Know this!
It ends here!
I will not allow you to
leave this mansion alive!
No! That's lunacy!
Luring me away from the Gutter Rat.
How very noble of you.
No matter.
I'll drain you dry, and your blood will
help me mend from this little adventure.
You climb the wall in vain, Jojo,
in your haste to flee from me.
All you have done is guaranteed your doom.
You will be consumed tonight
by the inferno below, or by me!
Father.
Father, rest in peace.
Let the rising smoke
guide your soul to heaven.
But first, please, lend me
your aid one final time.
Let the fire burn with your strength.
What does he mean to accomplish up there?
No, that's crazy!
You're throwing your life away!
Don't do it!
Don't do it, Jojo!
Any moment now.
Useless!
You fight as though you want to die!
In that moment, Jojo's short
life flashed before his eyes.
My lonely youth, my time with Dio.
You did me wrong time and again,
so now I'll settle the score.
The longer the fire burns, the
hotter it gets, and Jojo knows it.
He means to use the mansion
as a funeral pyre and
burn the devil faster than
he can replenish himself.
And now that the house is hot enough,
he's going to knock him back in.
Jojo!
How dare you lay your
hands on me, you insect!
The only home I've ever known
will be in ashes before the dawn.
Father is dead, and I am alone.
I have nothing left to
lose, but my life itself.
We go to the flames together, Dio!
I'll gladly die if it
means an end to your evil!
Die for nothing, fool!
All I lose by your sacrifice is
the blood I would have taken.
Blacken and burn among the bones
of your damnable father, Jojo!
I am a god in all but name.
With the powers at my command,
I will rule this world.
Thank you, brother, for this great boon.
Damn it!
Dio!
I'm not done with you!
Why won't you die already?
There's no escape, Dio!
You've brought this doom upon yourself!
This is the knife you
used to kill my father!
So as you did to the man who
raised us both, I now do unto you!
I've crushed his arm bones to
splinters, and he's already ablaze?
but his grip on me is
still that of a vice!
So be it, Jojo.
Consign us both unto the flames, but
perish knowing I will survive this moment?
for everything you have done.
Even this inferno cannot devour me!
Fulmer, lend me your power!
His desperate cry echoed in the night.
Whether urged on by his departed
father or heeding an instinct,
born of a long familiarity with
the home which burned around him?
he kicked, and that put
them right in line with...
What the?
The statue of the Joestar
family's guardian angel.
How could a worm like you?
I forgot who I was dealing with.
Bloody his nose, and he
comes back twice as fierce.
Jojo!
I had such plans for this world.
on such plans!
JoJo!
It's over.
You're alive.
You lucky bastard.
He did it!
JoJo bested him!
I'll be the roundabout.
The words will make you out and out.
I'll spend the day your way.
Call it morning, driving through the sun.
And in and out the valley.
The music dance and sing.
They make the children really ring.
I spend the day your way.
Call it morning, driving through the sun.
And in and out the valley.
In and around the lake.
Miles come out of the sky.
And they'll stand there.
One mile over.
We'll be there and we'll see you.
Ten and two summers.
We'll be there and laughing too.
Twenty, forty, five mile.
But we'll see, I'll be there with you!
There it is.
Courage is to look your fear in the eye!
Dio's evil, yeah, but
this guy is far worse!
Prepare for the carnage!
Who do I look like?
I beg of you, teach me how to wield it.